Kunal Vohra

Content Writer

Sector 50 Noida, 201301 +91 9891698628 Kunalvohra65@gmail.com

ABOUT

To work with enthusiasm, knowledge, and understanding, to build a successful career in the corporate sector, to attain a responsible, challenging, and rewarding position that provides opportunities for cross-functional learning, professional growth, advertisement, and valuable applications for my work experience and skills.

EXPERIENCE

Zomato, Gurgaon — Content associate

August 2021 - February 2022

- Worked on refining Zomato's partner restaurants' data, such as feature images, seating capacity, live event information, and so forth to improve customer experience by improving visual appeal and data correctness, and listing details such as CFT, address, and cuisines of restaurants in northern India.
- Assisting third-party service providers in obtaining accurate restaurant information. Analyzing appropriate recognition for restaurants to increase their market appeal. Handling content as the company's face to correct errors and mismanagement.

Talent Connected Worldwide, Noida — Content writer

April 2022 - March 2022

- Web content curated to showcase corporate boarding and increase visibility.
- Published inbound blogs for both narrow and wide TGs. Updated the post on search engine algorithm dynamics. Created 700-900 word informational articles that were plagiarism-free and consistently achieved low bounce rates.
- Interpreting and analyzing data using Google Keyword Planner, Google Analytics, MOZ, etc, and using observations to improve traffic. Contacting Third-Party Sites for Guest Blogs.

iFortis, Bengaluru — Marketing and sales intern

June 2022 - August 2022

• We analyzed market data and identified opportunities to impress

SKILLS

Hardworking

Constructive thinking

Leadership

Honesty

Problem Solving

Proofreading

Teamwork

AWARDS

Football Award in High School

LANGUAGES

English - Fluent

Hindi - Fluent

- our brand. Developing and implementing a B2B marketing strategy and overall communication plan.
- Consulted with key clients to work with frontline individuals to win discretionary efforts and improve productivity across the organization. Received and reviewed company submissions to gather information regarding cross-selling products.

EDUCATION

DPS Indirapuram, Indirapuram — Senior Secondary Education

2014

GPA 80.4%

Middlesex University, London — *Diploma in Bsc Computer Science (Hons)*

October 2014 - April 2016